A Guide to the Harry Harris Collection of Confederate Pay Vouchers, 1863
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Harry Harris Collection of Confederate Pay Vouchers, 1863
The Library of Virginia
19980
44 pages
Harry Harris
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Purchased 27 January 1928 from Harry Harris, 111 West Main Street, Richmond, Virginia.
Scope and Content
Collection of Confederate pay vouchers, 1863, gathered by Harry Harris of Richmond, Virginia, and consisting of 22 pay vouchers for individuals in the 22nd Virginia Infantry Battalion including two surgeons, the 40th Virginia Infantry Regiment, and the 47th Virginia Infantry Regiment. All of the vouchers provide the amount of pay and the date range for which pay was received. Two of the vouchers, for Private William A. Binford (b. ca. 1843) and Private Thomas F. Drumwright (b. ca. 1820) of the 22nd Battalion, were issued as part of military discharges and also provide physical descriptions, places of birth, ages, and occupations for both men.
Arrangement
Arranged chronologically.
Contents List
- Voucher No. 2, 1 January 186[3], Lieutenant John W. Rollins, Company E, 47th Virginia Infantry Regiment, for pay covering 30 June to 31 December 1862.
- Voucher No. 1, 1 January 186[3], Captain Edmund Logwood Wharton, Company C, 47th Virginia Infantry Regiment, for pay covering November 1862.
- Voucher No. 34, 2 January 1863, Lieutenant James Madison Scales [Scates], Company D, 40th Virginia Infantry Regiment, for pay covering 25 April to 31 December 1862.
- Voucher No. 7, 6 April 1863, Captain Alexander F. Haynes, Company G, 22nd Battalion Virginia Infantry, for pay covering 28 February to 31 March 1863.
- Voucher No. 9, 6 April 1863, Thomas Smith, adjutant, 22nd Battalion Virginia Infantry, for pay covering 31 January to 31 March 1863.
- Voucher No. 11, 6 April 1863, Lieutenant Alex S. Johnson, Company A, 22nd Battalion Virginia Infantry, for pay covering 28 February to 31 March 1863.
- Voucher No. 12, 7 April 1863, Captain John G. Turpin, A.C.S., 22nd Battalion Virginia Infantry, for pay covering 31 December 1862 to 31 March 1863.
- Voucher No. 13, 7 April 1863, William R. Weisiger, surgeon, 22nd Battalion Virginia Infantry, for pay covering 28 February to 31 March 1863.
- Voucher No. 14, 7 April 1863, N. R. James, assistant surgeon, 22nd Battalion Virginia Infantry, for pay covering 31 December 1862 to 31 March 1863.
- Voucher No. 15, 7 April 1863, Lieutenant Thomas Hatcher, Company A, 22nd Battalion Virginia Infantry, for pay covering 17 January to 31 March 1863.
- Voucher No. 16, 9 April 1863, Captain William G. Jackson, Company D, 22nd Battalion Virginia Infantry, for pay covering 31 December 1862 to 31 March 1863.
- Voucher No. 18, 9 April 1863, Private Thomas F. Drumwright, Company D, 22nd Battalion Virginia Infantry, for pay covering 28 February to 9 April 1863. Drumwright, eligible for a military discharge due to physical disability, certifies he received all monies due him.
- Voucher No. 17, 11 April 1863, Lieutenant Andrew J. Leftwich, Company G, 22nd Battalion Virginia Infantry, for pay covering 31 December 1862 to 31 March 1863.
- Voucher No. 19, 11 April 1863, Captain John F. Tompkins, Company A, 22nd Battalion Virginia Infantry, for pay covering 28 February to 31 March 1863.
- Voucher No. 20, 11 April 1863, Lieutenant William A. Pace, Company D, 22nd Battalion Virginia Infantry, for pay covering 31 December 1862 to 31 March 1863.
- Voucher No. 21, 11 April 1863, Private William A. Binford, Company E, 22nd Battalion Virginia Infantry, for pay covering 30 June to 31 October 1862. Binford, eligible for a military discharge for providing a substitute, certifies that he has received all monies due him.
- Voucher No. 22, 13 April 1863, Lieutenant James E. Johnson, Company G, 22nd Battalion Virginia Infantry, for pay covering 31 January to 31 March 1863.
- Voucher No. 23, 16 April 1863, Lieutenant Henry Thomas Wilkinson, Company E, 22nd Battalion Virginia Infantry, for pay covering 31 January to 31 March 1863.
- Voucher No. 24, 9 May 1863, Captain William G. Jackson, Company D, 22nd Battalion Virginia Infantry, for pay covering 31 March to 30 April 1863.
- Voucher No. 27, 9 May 1863, Lieutenant Thomas C. Jeter, Company G, 22nd Battalion Virginia Infantry, for pay covering 31 March to 30 April 1863.
- Voucher No. 32, 19 May 1863, Captain John F. Tompkins, Company A, 22nd Battalion Virginia Infantry, for pay covering 31 March to 30 April 1863.
- Voucher No. 33, 19 May 1863, Lieutenant Henry Thomas Wilkinson, Company E, 22nd Battalion Virginia Infantry, for pay covering 31 March to 30 April 1863.